<Document>
  # Core Rule 5 - ERP (Erotic Roleplay) is permitted, within reason
  [bold]This is a zero tolerance rule.[/bold]

  Erotic Roleplay (commonly abbreviated as "ERP") and sexual content is allowed, due to the gameplay content and nature of this server. However, there are still some restrictions and caveats that you must be aware of.

  ## The Golden Rule
  [bold]No means No.[/bold]
  
  If you are ever asked to stop for any reason, [bold]you must stop immediately[/bold]. If you do not, you will be banned.
  
  For clarity, the request to stop must be explicitly communicated through LOOC. Dubious non-consent could be permissable per character, but any out-of-character request to stop must be respected.

  ## What Is Allowed
  - ERP 'fluff text' through actions to enhance or give context to gameplay mechanics. For example, describing the specifics of coitus while performing a 'Penetrative' action.
  - General and brief sexual interactions, within the permissions of the other player(s) consent.
  - Sexual content in character names and descriptions.
  - IC (In Character) romance, dating and relationships.

  ## Allowed Content
  This list is non-exhaustive, but common sense applies. If you're unsure, ask an admin.
  - Anything vanilla.
  - Anything that the game server provides as a gameplay mechanic.

  ## What Is Not Allowed
  - Role abandonment to ERP for an entire round.
  - ERP that contains extreme content (see below).
  - ERP that is non-consensual. This includes bypassing the Consent System imposed by the game, or ERPing with players who have not given their explicit consent, or continuining to ERP with players who have asked you to stop Out-Of-Character.

  ## Extreme (Not Allowed) Content
  This list is non-exhaustive, but common sense applies. If you're unsure, ask an admin.
  - Underaged play. (All characters cannot be under the age of 18 anyway, don't pretend like they are.)
  - Scat, vomit or similar filth play.
  - ABDL (Adult Baby Diaper Lover) play.
</Document>
