<Document>
  [bold]Rule enforcement is currently relaxed during development/testing. However, still make yourselves aware for when the rules are enforced.[/bold]

  This server operates under a [italics]modified version[/italics] of the LRP/MRP Ruleset.

  Admin discretion is treated as 'LRP+' with a focus on fun and roleplay.

  Generally, most things are the same, but you should still familiarise yourself with the [textlink="Core Rules" link="CoreRules"] and [textlink="Roleplay Rules" link="RoleplayRules"].

  The following highlights some of the key rules you need to be aware of:

  ## You MUST be at least 18 years old
  See [textlink="Core Rule 1" link="RuleC1"].

  If you are under the age of 18, please do not join this server. [italics]Leave immediately[/italics]. Do not participate in this community. [bold]This is your only warning.[/bold]

  [bold]Violating this rule will result in a permanent, non-appealable ban.[/bold]

  ## ERP is allowed, but with restrictions
  See [textlink="Core Rule 5" link="RuleC5"].

  Due to the nature of this server, ERP [italics]is[/italics] permitted but fundementally this is still a SS14 game server. ERP is not the primary focus of the server, and you should still be aware of the rules and guidelines.

  ## Roles have expectations
  See [textlink="Roleplay Rule 12" link="RuleR12"] and [textlink="Roleplay Rule 13" link="RuleR13"].

  You are expected to play your role to the best of your ability. This includes following the rules and guidelines for your role. If you are unsure, ask an admin.

  ## Antagonists have expectations
  See [textlink="Roleplay Rule 9" link="RuleR9"].

  Amendments to antagonist objectives (namely traitors) has adjusted the expectations from antagonist players. You should be aware of these changes.

  # Be fun!
  SS14 can be a stressful and frustrating game, but ultimately it is supposed to be fun. Do everything to ensure that not only you have fun, but the people around you have fun as well!
</Document>
